{
    "results": [
    {
        "question": "Exercises for solo practice that lead to Kata and correct judo form",
        "correct_answer": "Tandoku Renshu",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Kusushi",
            "Waza",
            "Ashi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grip fighting form/technique",
        "correct_answer": "Kumi Kata",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ashi-waza",
            "Tachi-waza",
            "Kansetsu-waza"
        ]
    },
    {

        "question": "Standing techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Tachi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ne-waza",
            "Shime-waza",
            "Te-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Foot or leg techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Ashi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Ne-waza",
            "Shime-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Strangling techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Shime-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Kansetsu-waza",
            "Te-waza",
            "Kumi Kata"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hand techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Te-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Kansetsu-waza",
            "Ashi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hip techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Koshi-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ne-waza",
            "Nage no Kata",
            "Shime-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Technique",
        "correct_answer": "Waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Shime",
            "Tachi",
            "Koshi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Locking techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Kansetsu-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Shime-waza",
            "Te-waza",
            "Tachi-waza"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ground techniques",
        "correct_answer": "Ne-waza",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Koshi-waza",
            "Te-waza",
            "Koshi-waza"
        ]
    }]
}
